[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Katharine Hepburn movie was ranked number 5 in the American Film Institutes top 10 list of the greatest romantic movies of all time?", "correct_answer": "The Philadelphia Story", "incorrect_answers": ["Bringing Up Baby", "Olly Olly Oxen Free", "Woman of the Year"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these sharks has a flat body like a stingray?", "correct_answer": "angel shark", "incorrect_answers": ["basking shark", "blue shark", "blacktip reef shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Harry Potters best friend and schoolmate?", "correct_answer": "Ron Weasley", "incorrect_answers": ["Neville Longbottom", "Sirius Black", "Albus Dumbledore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A 1672 painting in Dobarsko in this country depicts Jesus in a rocket ship.", "correct_answer": "Bulgaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Croatia", "Hungary", "Estonia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On April 11, 2002, Al-Qaeda carried out a terrorist attack near a synagogue on which Tunisian island?", "correct_answer": "Djerba", "incorrect_answers": ["Yalikavak", "Salih Ada", "Kargi Adasi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Silver and gold are in the same group on the periodic table. What group are they in and what are their atomic symbols, respectively?", "correct_answer": "Group 11, Ag and Au", "incorrect_answers": ["Group 12, Ag and Au", "Group 14, Au and Ag", "Group 13, Au and Ag"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Sam Dawson in the movie I Am Sam?", "correct_answer": "Sean Penn", "incorrect_answers": ["Edward Norton", "Kevin Spacey", "Will Farrell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1987 movie directed by Peter Jackson involved aliens who wanted to use humans as meat for their fast food chain.", "correct_answer": "Bad Taste", "incorrect_answers": ["Basket Case", "McDougals", "The Beyond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is  true about the final scene of Rabbit Test?", "correct_answer": "It is staged as a Nativity scene.", "incorrect_answers": ["Gary Shandlings character becomes a stand-up comedian.", "The United Nations declares the films star a World Citizen for saving  the world from starvation.", "The rabbit farmer become President of the United States."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The common link between these four movies -Chicken Run, Harry Potter, The Mummy Returns and Cast Away, is that...?", "correct_answer": "They all are produced by one and the same company.", "incorrect_answers": ["They all treat one and the same social problem.", "One and the same actor is starring in all of them.", "They all refer to one and the same social class."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Blazing Saddles, the township finds out that Hedley Lamarr has gathered a group of ruthless thugs to destroy the town. What idea did the sheriff come up with to save the town?", "correct_answer": "He wanted to build a fake town", "incorrect_answers": ["He formed his own army.", "He rodes off into the sunset leaving the townsfolk to deal with the issue.", "He asked Hedley Lamarr to stop."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor voiced Makunga the Lion in the 2008 animated comedy movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "Alec Baldwin", "incorrect_answers": ["Bernie Mac", "Andy Richter", "David Schwimmer"]}]